<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>get on</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/</link><description>Recent content in get on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>artefacts</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/artefacts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/artefacts/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get artefacts [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;artefact-reference&amp;gt;} Options # -a, --attached show attached artefacts -h, --help help for artefacts -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow index nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fields Description # Get lists all artefact versions specified, if only a repository is specified all tagged artefacts are listed.
If the repository/registry option is specified, the given names are interpreted relative to the specified registry using the syntax</description></item><item><title>componentversions</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/componentversions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/componentversions/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get componentversions [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;component-reference&amp;gt;} Options # -h, --help help for componentversions --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -S, --scheme string schema version -s, --sort stringArray sort fields Description # Get lists all component versions specified, if only a component is specified all versions are listed.</description></item><item><title>credentials</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/credentials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/credentials/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get credentials {&amp;lt;consumer property&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt;} Options # -h, --help help for credentials -m, --matcher string matcher type override Description # Try to resolve a given consumer specification against the configured credential settings and show the found credential attributes.
For the following usage contexts with matchers and standard identity matchers exist:
Buildcredentials.ocm.software: Config credential matcher
It matches the Buildcredentials.ocm.software consumer type and additionally acts like the hostpath type.
OCIRegistry: OCI registry credential matcher</description></item><item><title>references</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/references/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/references/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get references [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }} Options # -h, --help help for references --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fields Description # Get references of a component version. References are specified by identities. An identity consists of a name argument followed by optional &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; arguments.</description></item><item><title>resources</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/resources/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/resources/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get resources [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }} Options # -h, --help help for resources --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, treewide, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fields Description # Get resources of a component version. Resources are specified by identities. An identity consists of a name argument followed by optional &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; arguments.</description></item><item><title>sources</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/sources/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:39:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/get/sources/</guid><description>Usage # ocm get sources [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }} Options # -h, --help help for sources --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fields Description # Get sources of a component version. Sources are specified by identities. An identity consists of a name argument followed by optional &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; arguments.</description></item></channel></rss>