<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transfer on</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/</link><description>Recent content in transfer on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:03:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>artifacts</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/artifacts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/artifacts/</guid><description>Usage # ocm transfer artifacts [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;artifact-reference&amp;gt;} &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; Options # -h, --help help for artifacts --repo string repository name or spec -R, --repo-name transfer repository name Description # Transfer OCI artifacts from one registry to another one. Several transfer scenarios are supported:
copy a set of artifacts (for the same repository) into another registry copy a set of artifacts (for the same repository) into another repository copy artifacts from multiple repositories into another registry copy artifacts from multiple repositories into another registry with a given repository prefix (option -R) By default the target is seen as a single repository if a repository is specified.</description></item><item><title>commontransportarchive</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/commontransportarchive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/commontransportarchive/</guid><description>Usage # ocm transfer commontransportarchive [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;ctf&amp;gt; &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; Options # -V, --copy-resources transfer referenced resources by-value -h, --help help for commontransportarchive -f, --overwrite overwrite existing component versions --script string config name of transfer handler script -s, --scriptFile string filename of transfer handler script -t, --type string archive format (directory, tar, tgz) (default &amp;quot;directory&amp;quot;) --uploader &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; repository uploader (&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;artifact type&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;media type&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;JSON target config) (default []) Description # Transfer content of a Common Transport Archive to the given target repository.</description></item><item><title>componentarchive</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/componentarchive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/componentarchive/</guid><description>Usage # ocm transfer componentarchive [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;source&amp;gt; &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; Options # -h, --help help for componentarchive -t, --type string archive format (directory, tar, tgz) (default &amp;quot;directory&amp;quot;) Description # Transfer a component archive to some component repository. This might be a CTF Archive or a regular repository. If the type CTF is specified the target must already exist, if CTF flavor is specified it will be created if it does not exist.</description></item><item><title>componentversions</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/componentversions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli/transfer/componentversions/</guid><description>Usage # ocm transfer componentversions [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;component-reference&amp;gt;} &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; Options # -c, --constraints constraints version constraint -V, --copy-resources transfer referenced resources by-value -h, --help help for componentversions --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -f, --overwrite overwrite existing component versions -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec --script string config name of transfer handler script -s, --scriptFile string filename of transfer handler script -t, --type string archive format (directory, tar, tgz) (default &amp;quot;directory&amp;quot;) --uploader &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; repository uploader (&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;artifact type&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;media type&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;JSON target config) (default []) Description # Transfer all component versions specified to the given target repository.</description></item></channel></rss>