<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mpas on</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/</link><description>Recent content in Mpas on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:45:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/mpas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MPAS Demo Video</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/demo_of_mpas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/mpas/demo_of_mpas/</guid><description>Demo of MPAS</description></item><item><title>Core Concepts</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/core_concepts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:37:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/mpas/core_concepts/</guid><description>This section describes the core concepts of MPAS and what Kubernetes controllers and custom resources are contained. To learn more about the MPAS architecture, see Architecture.
Product # A Product is a package of software that can be deployed to target environments such as Kubernetes clusters, virtual machines or bare-metal devices.
Products are made available to the MPAS system as OCM Components via a Subscription. Multiple instances of a Product may be installed that refer to the same Subscription.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:37:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/mpas/installation/</guid><description>Install using Binaries # To install the MPAS CLI, you can download the binaries for major platforms from the GitHub releases page.
Homebrew # You can also install via homebrew for macOS and Linux:
brew install open-component-model/tap/mpas
Bash # To install with bash for macOS or Linux execute the following command:
curl -sfL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/open-component-model/mpas/main/install.sh | sh -</description></item><item><title>Get Started with MPAS</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/getting_started/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:37:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/mpas/getting_started/</guid><description>This tutorial shows you how to bootstrap MPAS to a Kubernetes cluster and deploy a simple application.
Prerequisites # A Kubernetes cluster A GitHub access token with repo scope kubectl Objectives # Bootstrap MPAS to a Kubernetes cluster Deploy a simple application Install the MPAS CLI # The MPAS CLI is the primary tool for interacting with MPAS. It can be used to bootstrap MPAS to a Kubernetes cluster.
To install the MPAS CLI using brew:</description></item><item><title>Bootstrap</title><link>https://ocm.software/mpas/bootstrap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 10:37:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/mpas/bootstrap/</guid><description>The mpas bootstrap command deploys the following components to your cluster:
Flux: A Kubernetes operator that will install and manage the other components. ocm-controller: A Kubernetes controller that enables the automated deployment of software using the Open Component Model and Flux. git-controller: A Kubernetes controller that will create pull requests in the target Github repository when changes are made to the cluster. replication-controller: A Kubernetes controller that replicates everything defined and bundled in an OCM component version (and that the consumer subscribed to) into the local OCI registry of the cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>