<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/extensionpoints/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/extensionpoints/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/functional/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/functional/</guid><description>Functional Extension Points of the Open Component Model Specification # The specification is based on 4 basic functional extension points:
The storage backend technologies to use to store OCM elements (available mapping specifications can be found in appendix A). Access to artifact content using different storage technologies. This is described by types access specifications (types with available implementations can be found in appendix B). Digest calculation for dedicated content technologies requiring digests different from standard byte sequence digests of artifact blobs (defined digest types can be found in appendix C).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/semantic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://symmetrical-broccoli-b4446266.pages.github.io/spec/extensionpoints/semantic/</guid><description>Semantic Extension Points of the Open Component Model Specification # The specification is based on two basic extension points for describing semantics of artifacts:
Formal artifact types describe the technical meaning of an artifact, independent of their technical representation in a blob format (centrally defined types are described in appendix E). Dynamic attribution of artifacts with additional formal information not directly described by elements of the Open Component Model is possible with labels.</description></item></channel></rss>